[
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_02",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_01",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99F_MSQ_12",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_FreePrisoner_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ01_FreePrisoner_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_02",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_02",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_01",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_GatherRelics_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ02_GatherRelics_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Yash_02",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_03",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_02",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_AttackMentally_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ03_AttackMentally_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Phaeris_03",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_04",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_03",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_HealAlly_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "HoningStoneT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 5,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ04_HealAlly_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Morgaine_04",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_05",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_04",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_ReconnectHive_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ05_ReconnectHive_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Sun_01",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_06",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_05",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_ActivateCrystals_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ06_ActivateCrystals_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_04",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_07",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_06",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_PlantBombs_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ07_PlantBombs_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_05",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_08",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_07",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_ExcavateArtifacts_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "earringshatteredmountainT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ08_ExcavateArtifacts_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_05",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_alt",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_05",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_09",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_08",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_PrepareWarfare_alt_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 10,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ09_PrepareWarfare_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Russo_06",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_10",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_09",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_AssaultStronghold_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "PotionHealthT5",
		"ItemRewardQty": 15,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ10_AssaultStronghold_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "99G_Grace_02",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_10",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_DestroyEnemy_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Legwear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ11_DestroyEnemy_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
		"NOTE": "Soul Trial"
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Headgear_65",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_destroyer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Warmonger",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_destroyer",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_musketeer",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Musketeer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_musketeer",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_mystic",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Theurgist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_mystic",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_occultist",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Occultist",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_occultist",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_ranger",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Tracker",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_ranger",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_soldier",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Mercenary",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_soldier",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_swordsman",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_container",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_11 && Archetype_Wanderer",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_BidFarewell_success_swordsman",
		"ItemRewardName": "CRX_RewardContainerT5_Weapons_60",
		"ItemRewardQty": 1,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ12_BidFarewell_Grace_TalkTo_Start_Greet",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	},
	{
		"ObjectiveID": "99G_MSQ_SM_DesertVector",
		"Type": "MainStoryQuest",
		"DifficultyLevel": 60,
		"Task": "99G_MSQ_SM_DesertVector_container",
		"NpcDestinationId": "1625_Ghazi_p1",
		"AchievementId": "99G_MSQ_13",
		"RequiredAchievementId": "99G_MSQ_12",
		"SuccessGameEventId": "99G_MSQ_SM_DesertVector_success",
		"ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
		"ItemRewardQty": 200,
		"CanBeAbandoned": false,
		"Title": "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_title",
		"Description": "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_desc",
		"PlayerPrompt": "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_start_prompt",
		"ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_proposal",
		"InProgressResponse": "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_incomplete",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
		"DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@99G_MSQ13_DesertVector_complete",
		"HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
	}
]